[
  {
    "Question" : "Scale up to find a fraction equivalent to 2/7 with the denominator 56.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Scale up to find a fraction equivalent to two-sevenths with the denominator 56.",
    "Type" : "Scaling Up",
    "Difficulty Level" : 2,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 16,
         "Denominator" : 56
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 1/3 can scale up to the fraction 2/6.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, one-third can scale up to the fraction two-sixths.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to find an equivalent fraction, you need to multiply the numerator and denominator by the same number.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to find an equivalent fraction, you need to multiply the numerator and denominator by the same number.",
         "Hint3" : "Try multiplying the numerator and denominator of 2/7 by 8.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "Try multiplying the numerator and denominator of two-sevenths by 8."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixteen-fifty-sixths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "For this problem, you multiply the numerator 2 and the denominator 7 of the fraction by 8 to get the equivalent fraction, which gives you the answer.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "For this problem, you multiply the numerator 2 and the denominator 7 of the fraction by 8 to get the equivalent fraction, which gives you the answer."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Scale down to find the simplest fraction equivalent to 16/48.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Scale down to find the simplest fraction equivalent to sixteen-forty-eighths.",
    "Type" : "Scaling Down",
    "Difficulty Level" : 2,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 1,
         "Denominator" : 3
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 4/6 can scale down to the simplest fraction 2/3.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, four-sixths can scale down to the simplest fraction two-thirds.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to find the simplest fraction, you need to divide the numerator and denominator by the same number.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to find the simplest fraction, you need to divide the numerator and denominator by the same number.",
         "Hint3" : "Try dividing the numerator and denominator of 16/48 by 16.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "Try dividing the numerator and denominator of sixteen-forty-eighths by 16."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one-third.",
    "Written Explanation" : "To do this problem, you divide the numerator 16 and the denominator 48 each by 16. This gives you the simplest fraction.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "To do this problem, you divide the numerator 16 and the denominator 48 each by 16. This gives you the simplest fraction."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Find the least common denominator of 3/4 and 3/16.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Find the least common denominator of three-fourths and three-sixteenths.",
    "Type" : "Common Denominator",
    "Difficulty Level" : 1,
    "Format" : "value",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Value" : 16
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, the common denominator of 1/2 and 1/3 is 6.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, the common denominator of one-half and one-third is 6.",
         "Hint2" : "You need to find the smallest number that is a multiple of both denominators.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "You need to find the smallest number that is a multiple of both denominators.",
         "Hint3" : "Try listing out the multiples of the denominators. The multiples of 4 are 4, 8, 12, ... and the multiples of 16 are 16, 32, 48, ... Where do the two lists match up?",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "Try listing out the multiples of the denominators. The multiples of 4 are 4, 8, 12, and so on, and the multiples of 16 are 16, 32, 48, and so on. Where do the two lists match up?"
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is 16.",
    "Written Explanation" : "When you list the multiples of the denominators, 4 and 16, the two lists first match up at the number 16, meaning that this is the least common denominator of the two fractions.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "When you list the multiples of the denominators, 4 and 16, the two lists first match up at the number 16, meaning that this is the least common denominator of the two fractions."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Find the least common denominator of 1/7 and 4 1/6.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Find the least common denominator of one-sevenths and four and one-sixth.",
    "Type" : "Common Denominator",
    "Difficulty Level" : 3,
    "Format" : "value",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Value" : 42
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, the common denominator of 2/4 and 1/3 is 12.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, the common denominator of two-fourths and one-third is 12.",
         "Hint2" : "You need to find the smallest number that is a multiple of both denominators. Do not worry about the whole number.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "You need to find the smallest number that is a multiple of both denominators. Do not worry about the whole number.",
         "Hint3" : "Try listing out the multiples of the denominators. The multiples of 7 are 7, 14, 21, ... and the multiples of 6 are 6, 12, 18, ... Where do the two lists match up?",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "Try listing out the multiples of the denominators. The multiples of 7 are 7, 14, 21, and so on, and the multiples of 6 are 6, 12, 18, and so on. Where do the two lists match up?"
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is 42.",
    "Written Explanation" : "When you list the multiples of the denominators, 7 and 6, the two lists first match up at the number 42, meaning that this is the least common denominator of the two fractions.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "When you list the multiples of the denominators, 7 and 6, the two lists first match up at the number 42, meaning that this is the least common denominator of the two fractions."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Convert the mixed number 4 3/10 to an improper fraction.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Convert the mixed number four and three-tenths to an improper fraction.",
    "Type" : "Conversion",
    "Difficulty Level" : 2,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 43,
         "Denominator" : 10
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 1 1/4 can be converted to the improper fraction 5/4.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, one and one-fourth can be converted to the improper fraction five-fourths.",
         "Hint2" : "The first step is to multiply the denominator by the whole number. What should you do next?",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "The first step is to multiply the denominator by the whole number. What should you do next?",
         "Hint3" : "After multiplying the denominator and whole number, add that to the numerator.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "After multiplying the denominator and whole number, add that to the numerator."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-three-tenths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "For this problem, you first multiply the denominator 10 by the whole number 4 and then add this to the numerator 3. 10 times 4 plus 3 is 43. The denominator stays the same.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "For this problem, you first multiply the denominator 10 by the whole number 4 and then add this to the numerator 3. 10 times 4 plus 3 is 43. The denominator stays the same."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Convert the mixed number 11 4/5 to an improper fraction.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Convert the mixed number eleven and four-fifths to an improper fraction.",
    "Type" : "Conversion",
    "Difficulty Level" : 3,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 59,
         "Denominator" : 5
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 2 1/3 can be converted to the improper fraction 7/3.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, two and one-third can be converted to the improper fraction seven-thirds.",
         "Hint2" : "The first step is to multiply the denominator by the whole number. What should you do next?",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "The first step is to multiply the denominator by the whole number. What should you do next?",
         "Hint3" : "After multiplying the denominator and whole number, add that to the numerator.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "After multiplying the denominator and whole number, add that to the numerator."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-nine-fifths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "First, you multiply the denominator 5 by the whole number 11 and then add this to the numerator 4. 5 times 11 plus 4 is 59. The denominator stays the same.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "First, you multiply the denominator 5 by the whole number 11 and then add this to the numerator 4. 5 times 11 plus 4 is 59. The denominator stays the same."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "3 2/10 + 3/4 = 
    Write your answer as an improper fraction in lowest terms.",
    "Spoken Question" : "What is three and two-tenths plus three-fourths? Write your answer in lowest terms.",
    "Type" : "Adding Unlike Denominators",
    "Difficulty Level" : 1,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 79,
         "Denominator" : 20
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 1/2 + 1/4 = 3/4.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, one-half plus one-fourth equals three-fourths.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to add two fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to add two fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator.",
         "Hint3" : "The common denominator of the two fractions is 20. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Remember to express your answer as an improper fraction.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "The common denominator of the two fractions is 20. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Remember to express your answer as an improper fraction."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-nine-twentieths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "In this problem, the two fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 20. 2/10 can be written as 4/20, and 3/4 can be written as 15/20. Then, 3 4/20 + 15/20 gives you 3 19/20, which is equal to the improper fraction 79/20.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "In this problem, the two fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 20. Two-tenths can be written as four-twentieths, and three-fourths can be written as fifteen-twentieths. Then, three and four-twentieths plus fifteen-twentieths gives you three and nineteen-twentieths, which is equal to the improper fraction seventy-nine-twentieths."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Adam ate 15/10 pizzas, Bill ate 3/5 of a pizza, and Casper ate 5/2 pizzas. How much pizza did they eat in total? Leave your answer as an improper fraction in lowest terms.",
    "Spoken Question" : "Adam ate fifteen-tenths pizzas, Bill ate three-fifths of a pizza, and Casper ate five-halves pizzas. How much pizza did they eat in total? Leave your answer as an improper fraction in lowest terms.",
    "Type" : "Adding Unlike Denominators Word Problem",
    "Difficulty Level" : 2,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 23,
         "Denominator" : 5
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 3/8 + 1/2 = 7/8.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, three-eighths plus one-half equals seven-eighths.",
         "Hint2" : "You first need to find the common denominator of the three fractions.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "You first need to find the common denominator of the three fractions.",
         "Hint3" : "The common denominator is 10. Once you add the fractions, remember that your answer should be in lowest terms.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "The common denominator is 10. Once you add the fractions, remember that your answer should be in lowest terms."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-three-fifths.",
    "Written Explanation" : "This is an addition problem, because we want to know how much pizza was eaten in total. 3/5 can be written as 6/10, and 5/2 can be written as 25/10. Together, this adds up to 46/10, which can be simplified to 23/5.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "This is an addition problem, because we want to know how much pizza was eaten in total. Three-fifths can be written as six-tenths, and five-halves can be written as twenty-five-tenths. Together, this adds up to forty-six-tenths, which can be simplified to twenty-three-fifths."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "1 3/8 + 3 2/7 = 
    Write your answer as an improper fraction in lowest terms.",
    "Spoken Question" : "What is one and three-eighths plus three and two-sevenths? Write your answer as an improper fraction in lowest terms.",
    "Type" : "Adding Unlike Denominators",
    "Difficulty Level" : 3,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 261,
         "Denominator" : 56
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 1 2/3 + 1 1/4 = 2 11/12, or 35/12.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, one and two-thirds plus one and one-fourth equals two and eleven-twelfths, or thirty-five-twelfths.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to add fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator. First add the fractions, then worry about the whole numbers.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to add fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator. First add the fractions, then worry about the whole numbers.",
         "Hint3" : "The common denominator of the fractions is 56. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Once you get the answer, you need to convert it from a mixed number to an improper fraction.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "The common denominator of the fractions is 56. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Once you get the answer, you need to convert it from a mixed number to an improper fraction."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is two hundred sixty-one over fifty-six.",
    "Written Explanation" : "Since the two fractions have different denominators, you need to find their common denominator, which is 56. 3/8 can be written as 21/56, and 2/7 can be written as 16/56. Then, 1 21/56 plus 3 16/56 equals 4 37/56. Then, you convert this to an improper fraction, which gives you 261/56.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "Since the two fractions have different denominators, you need to find their common denominator, which is 56. 3/8 can be written as 21/56, and 2/7 can be written as 16/56. Then, one and twenty-one-fifty-sixths plus three and sixteen-fifty-sixths equals four and thirty-seven-fifty-sixths. Then, you convert this to an improper fraction, which gives you two hundred sixty-one over fifty-six."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "3 5/7 - 1 2/3 = 
    Write your answer as an improper fraction in lowest terms.",
    "Spoken Question" : "What is three and five-sevenths minus one and two-thirds? Write your answer as an improper fraction in lowest terms.",
    "Type" : "Subtracting Unlike Denominators",
    "Difficulty Level" : 1,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 43,
         "Denominator" : 21
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 1/2 - 1/4 = 1/4.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, one-half minus one-fourth equals one-fourth.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to subtract two fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator. First deal with the fractions, then worry about the whole numbers.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to subtract two fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator. First deal with the fractions, then worry about the whole numbers.",
         "Hint3" : "The common denominator of the two fractions is 21. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Once you subtract the fractions and whole numbers, remember that your answer should be an improper fraction.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "The common denominator of the two fractions is 21. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Once you subtract the fractions and whole numbers, remember that your answer should be an improper fraction."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-three-twenty-firsts.",
    "Written Explanation" : "The two fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 21. 5/7 can be written as 15/21, and 2/3 can be written as 14/21. Then, 3 15/21 - 1 14/21 gives you 2 1/21, which is equal to the improper fraction 43/21.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "The two fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 21. Five-sevenths can be written as fifteen-twenty-firsts, and two-thirds can be written as fourteen-twenty-firsts. Then, three and fifteen-twenty-firsts minus one and fourteen-twenty-firsts gives two and one-twenty-first, which is equal to the improper fraction forty-three-twenty-firsts."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "Derek drank 1 5/14 cups of milk, and Pam drank 1 2/7 cups of milk. How many more cups of milk did Derek drink than Pam?",
    "Spoken Question" : "Derek drank one and five-fourteenths cups of milk, and Pam drank one and two-fourteenths cups of milk. How many more cups of milk did Derek drink than Pam?",
    "Type" : "Subtracting Like Denominators Word Problem",
    "Difficulty Level" : 2,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 1,
         "Denominator" : 14
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 2/5 - 3/10 = 1/10.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, two-fifths minus three-tenths equals one-tenth.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to subtract two fractions, you should first find the common denominator.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to subtract two fractions, you should first find the common denominator.",
         "Hint3" : "The common denominator is 14. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Remember to subtract the fractions and the whole numbers.",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "The common denominator is 14. Now make both fractions have the same denominator. Remember to subtract the fractions and the whole numbers."
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one-fourteenth.",
    "Written Explanation" : "This is a subtraction problem, since you want to know how much more Derek drank. 2/7 can be written as 4/14. Then, 1 5/14 minus 1 4/14 gives you the answer.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "This is a subtraction problem, since you want to know how much more Derek drank. Two-sevenths can be written as four-fourteenths. Then, one and five-fourteenths minus one and four-fourteenths gives you the answer."
  },

  {
    "Question" : "4 15/16 - 2/3 - 1/8 = 
    Write your answer as an improper fraction in lowest terms.",
    "Spoken Question" : "What is four and fifteen-sixteenths minus two-thirds minus one-eighth? Write your answer as an improper fraction in lowest terms.",
    "Type" : "Subtracting Unlike Denominators",
    "Difficulty Level" : 3,
    "Format" : "fraction",
    "Answer" :
    {
         "Numerator" : 199,
         "Denominator" : 48
    },
    "Hints" :
    {
         "Hint1" : "For example, 3 2/3 - 1 1/4 = 2 5/12, which is equal to 29/12.",
         "Spoken Hint1" : "For example, three and two-thirds minus one and one-fourth equals two and five-twelfths, which is equal to twenty-nine-twelfths.",
         "Hint2" : "In order to subtract fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator. First subtract the fractions, then worry about the whole numbers.",
         "Spoken Hint2" : "In order to subtract fractions with different denominators, you need to find the common denominator. First subtract the fractions, then worry about the whole numbers.",
         "Hint3" : "The common denominator of the three fractions is 48. Now make the fractions have the same denominator. First subtract the fractions, then subtract the whole numbers. Remember to make your answer an improper fraction!",
         "Spoken Hint3" : "The common denominator of the three fractions is 48. Now make the fractions have the same denominator. First subtract the fractions, then subtract the whole numbers. Remember to make your answer an improper fraction!"
    },
    "Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred ninety-nine over forty-eight.",
    "Written Explanation" : "The fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 48. 15/16 can be written as 45/48, 2/3 can be written as 32/48, and 1/8 can be written as 6/48. Then, 4 45/48 - 32/48 - 6/48 gives you 4 7/48, which is equal to the improper fraction 199/48.",
    "Spoken Explanation" : "The fractions have different denominators, and their common denominator is 48. Fifteen-sixteenths can be written as forty-five-forty-eighths, two-thirds can be written as thirty-two-forty-eighths, and one-eighth can be written as six-forty-eighths. Then, four and forty-five-forty-eighths minus thirty-two-forty-eighths minus six-forty-eighths gives you four and seven-forty-eighths, which is equal to the improper fraction one hundred ninety-nine over forty-eight."
  }
]